ugamsolutions.com 2019-07-14

# Ugam - Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 2018

##### What information do we collect?

We collect only the required personal information from you when you fill out a website form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: first name, last name, company, job title, e-mail address and phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

##### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to send periodic emails. The email address you provide for your request, may be used to send you Content, information and updates pertaining to your request, in addition to receiving monthly newsletters, occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

**Note:** If at any time you would like to opt-out from receiving future emails, we include detailed instructions at the bottom of each email. You may also write to [info@ugamsolutions.com](mailto:info@ugamsolutions.com) to opt-out of any email communication.

Content may mean an eBook, Case Study, Blog, Webinar, Whitepaper, Press Release or news articles, solutions, product information or demo, any web page, document or any other information displayed or available on the website.

##### Your consent

We will not collect, store, manage, process data or contact you through email or phone for product or services related sales outreach, without your explicit and deliberate consent, which you provide while filling a website form. 

##### Your rights

You can, at any time, exercise your right to access your information, request a copy of personal information we hold about you, unsubscribe or request to withdraw consent, right to rectification, erasure, to be forgotten, to restrict data processing and to object data processing. You can communicate any of the above requests to us by writing to [info@ugamsolutions.com](mailto:info@ugamsolutions.com) as mentioned in our website. Your request will be responded within 72 hours.

##### Data retention

Your data is retained by us only for marketing, sales and career-related purposes as consented by you and is deleted once you unsubscribe. 

##### How do we protect your information?

We adopt reasonable security practices and procedures, to include, technical, operational, managerial and physical security controls in order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, or disclosure while it is under our control.

We adhere to GDPR & ISO 27001 standards for security best practices. We have specialized security teams who constantly review and improve our measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, accidental loss, disclosure or destruction.

We take steps to ensure that our contracted third parties adopt reasonable level of security practices and procedures to ensure security of personal information. 

When we dispose of your personal information, we use reasonable procedures to erase it or render it unreadable.

No data transmission over the Internet is completely secure and for reasons outside of our control, security risks may still arise. Any personal information transmitted to us or from our online products or services will therefore be at your own risk. However, we will strive to ensure the security of your information. We observe reasonable security measures to protect your personal information against hacking and virus dissemination.

##### Do we use cookies?

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website so you do not have to re-enter your information each time you visit our site. We do not sell any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. 

Once you submit any of the forms on this website, we keep a record of your activity on this website. This may include Content viewed by you, your I.P. address, pages visited by you, how long were you on a particular page, in what order were the pages viewed, number of times you visited the website, etc. This is a record of your visit only on www.ugamsolutions.com, not any other website. 

##### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We work with third party vendors that are GDPR-compliant or adhere to high standards of data privacy and protection.

##### Acceptance of these Conditions

It is assumed that you have carefully read this document and agree to its contents. If you disagree with any part of this privacy policy, please refrain from using our website. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy as and when necessary. Continued use of our website and platform implies acceptance of the revised privacy policy.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

##### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us by writing to [info@ugamsolutions.com](mailto:info@ugamsolutions.com.).
